{
    "subject": "resource/Kyushu_Railway_Company",
    "predicate": "ontology/foundingDate",
    "object": "1987-04-01",
    "human_readable": "The Kyushu Railway Company was founded on April 1, 1987.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9625380039215088,
            "question": "When was the Kyushu Railway Company founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9374731183052063,
            "question": "Which company was founded on April 1, 1987?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9350839257240295,
            "question": "On what date was the Kyushu Railway Company established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9326505661010742,
            "question": "What is the founding date of the Kyushu Railway Company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9032535552978516,
            "question": "Is there a specific date associated with the founding of the Kyushu Railway Company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8745999932289124,
            "question": "What is the name of the railway company founded in 1987?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8068996071815491,
            "question": "In what year did the Kyushu Railway Company begin operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.733234703540802,
            "question": "What company was established in 1987?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6906020045280457,
            "question": "What significant event occurred on April 1st, 1987?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42710039019584656,
            "question": "April 1st holds significance for which company?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Kyushu Railway Company was founded on April 1, 1987.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7131_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What significant event occurred on April 1st, 1987?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7131_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What company was established in 1987?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7131_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did the Kyushu Railway Company begin operations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7131_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7131_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7131_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7131_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7131_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7131_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7131_158.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7131_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7131_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7131_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7131_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all of the documents provided as context information mention that JR Kyushu (which is synonymous with The Kyushu Railway Company) was formed in 1987, either through privatization or when Japanese National Railways was divided."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document `60.txt` states that JR Kyushu (Kyushu Railway Company) was created in 1987 when JNR was privatized. The document `93.txt` provides more detail, confirming that JR Kyushu was formed from the previous JNR lines that ran in Kyushu on April 1, 1987. Therefore, the information supports the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}